<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Epson Retail POS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_warn_receipt_near_end">Roll paper is nearly end.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_warn_battery_near_end">Battery level of printer is low.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_no_response">Please check the connection of the printer and the mobile terminal.\nConnection get lost.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_cover_open">Please close roll paper cover.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_receipt_end">Please check roll paper.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_paper_feed">Please release a paper feed switch.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_autocutter">Please remove jammed paper and close roll paper cover.\nRemove any jammed paper or foreign substances in the printer, and then turn the printer off and turn the printer on again.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_need_recover">Then, If the printer doesn\'t recover from error, please restart the printer.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_unrecover">Please restart the printer.\nIf same errors occurred after printer restarted, the printer may out of order.</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_overheat">Please wait until error LED of the printer turns off. \n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_head">Print head of printer is hot.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_motor">Motor Driver IC of printer is hot.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_battery">Battery of printer is hot.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_wrong_paper">Please set correct roll paper.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_battery_real_end">Please connect AC adapter or change the battery.\nBattery of printer is almost empty.\n</string>
    <string name="handlingmsg_err_offline">Printer is offline.\n</string>
    <string name="btn_maintenance_counter_and_printer_setting">Maintenance Counter &amp; Printer Setting</string>
    <string name="btn_firmware_update">Firmware Update</string>
    <string name="progress_msg">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="error_msg">Unexpected Error Occurred.\nStart Over Again.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_firm_update">Setting API do not support POS terminal model</string>
    <string name="note1_1">The time required to update depends on the interface.</string>
    <string name="note1_2">About 15 minutes for a network connection</string>
    <string name="note1_3">About 85 minutes for a Bluetooth connection</string>
    <string name="note2">You cannot stop the update once it has started.</string>
    <string name="note3">Check that the smart device is charged sufficiently.</string>
    <string name="note4">Check that no errors have occurred in the printer.</string>
    <string name="note5">Check that the printer\'s communication status is in good condition.</string>
    <string name="note6">Do not operate the smart device while updating the firmware.</string>
    <string name="note7">Do not turn off the printer while updating the firmware.</string>
    <string name="note8">Do not disconnect the connection cable and power cable while updating the firmware.</string>
    <string name="note9">Do not sleep the smart device while updating the firmware.</string>
    <string name="reconnect_message">Reconnecting Printer.</string>
    <string name="verify_message">Verify Firmware version.</string>
    <string name="title_firmware_update">Firmware Update</string>
    <string name="title_current_firmware">Current Firmware</string>
    <string name="title_target_firmware">Target Firmware</string>
    <string name="title_printer_model">Printer Model</string>
    <string name="title_firmware_list">Firmware List</string>
    <string name="btn_get_printer_firmware">Get Printer Firmware</string>
    <string name="btn_download_firmware_list">Download Firmware List</string>
    <string name="btn_update_firmware">Update Firmware</string>
    <string name="default_printerModel">TM-m10</string>

    <string name="test_comm">Printer Communication Test is Successful!</string>

    <!-- string related to UI-->
    <!-- Registration Form-->
    <string name="registration_form_title">Registration Form</string>
    <string name="registration_form_company_name">Company Name</string>
    <string name="registration_form_address">Address</string>
    <string name="registration_form_hp_no">Handphone No.</string>
    <string name="registration_form_email">Email</string>
    <string name="registration_form_serial_no">Serial Number</string>
    <string name="registration_form_verify_serial_no">Verify Serial Number</string>
    <string name="registration_form_username">Username</string>
    <string name="registration_form_password">Password</string>
    <string name="registration_form_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="registration_form_register">Register</string>

    <!--Search for Stock-->
    <string name="stock_search_form_title">Search for Stock</string>

    <!--Print Receipt-->
    <string name="print_receipt">Print Receipt</string>

    <!--Company Information-->
    <string name="company_info_title">Company Information</string>
    <string name="company_info_save">Save</string>
    <string name="company_info_website">Website</string>

    <!--Report-->
    <string name="report_title">Report</string>
    <string name="report_category">Report Category</string>
    <string name="report_margin_title">Margin Report</string>
    <string name="report_purchase_title">Purchase Report</string>
    <string name="report_sales_title">Sales Report</string>
    <string name="report_ranking_title">Ranking Report</string>
    <string name="report_inventory_title">Inventory Report</string>
    <string name="report_date">Date</string>
    <string name="report_from_date">From Date</string>
    <string name="report_to_date">To Date</string>
    <string name="report_trans_no">Trans No</string>
    <string name="report_trans_code">Trans Code</string>
    <string name="report_name">Name</string>
    <string name="report_amount">Amount</string>
    <string name="report_sales">Sales</string>
    <string name="report_ranking_sold">Sold</string>
    <string name="report_ranking_code">Code</string>
    <string name="report_buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="report_profit">Profit</string>
    <string name="report_total">Total</string>
    <string name="report_total_sales">Total Sales</string>
    <string name="report_total_capital">Total Capital</string>
    <string name="report_total_profit">Total Profit</string>
    <string name="report_export">Export</string>

    <!--Main Screen-->
    <string name="main_total_sales">Total Sales</string>
    <string name="main_inventory">Inventory</string>
    <string name="main_sales">Sales</string>
    <string name="main_setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="main_report">Report</string>
    <string name="main_exit">Exit</string>

    <!--Login Screen-->
    <string name="username_email">Username or Email</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="login_to_application">Login to Application</string>
    <string name="do_not_have_account">Do Not Have Account?</string>

    <!--purchasing screen-->
    <string name="purchasing_title">Purchasing</string>

    <!--Setting screen-->
    <string name="setting_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_big_title">Application Settings</string>

    <!--Account registration/Daftar Pengguna-->
    <string name="user_account">User Account</string>
    <string name="user_account_registration">User Account Registration</string>

    <!--Sales Record-->
    <string name="sales_record_title">Sales Record</string>

    <!--Month-->
    <string name="January">January</string>
    <string name="February">February</string>
    <string name="March">March</string>
    <string name="April">April</string>
    <string name="May">May</string>
    <string name="June">June</string>
    <string name="July">July</string>
    <string name="August">August</string>
    <string name="September">September</string>
    <string name="October">October</string>
    <string name="November">November</string>
    <string name="December">December</string>

    <!--Toast messages-->
    <string name="process_rejected">Process rejected, you do not have the access right</string>

    <!--alert dialog message-->
    <string name="alert_dialog_Confirmation">Confirmation</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_main_exit">Do you want to exit the application ?</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_no">No</string>
    <string name="alert_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="denomination1">2</string>
    <string name="denomination2">5</string>
    <string name="denomination3">10</string>
    <string name="denomination4">50</string>
    <string name="denomination5">100</string>

    <string name="currency">$</string>
    <string name="termsofuse">
These Terms of Use, together with the documents referenced herein (collectively the "Terms"), apply to the mobile application named "Retail POS" (the "App"). PT Epson Indonesia (hereinafter referred to as "EIN" and/or "we") permits you to use the App in connection with the use of the Epson TM Printer (the “Purpose”) and subject to these Terms and any applicable rules applied by and Google Inc. ("Play Store Rules") with respect to the use of the Google Play Store (the “Play Store”). You (hereinafter referred to as "you" and/or the “App user”) may only use the App in accordance with these Terms.

1.	IMPORTANT NOTICES:

1.1	Please read these Terms carefully before downloading, installing or using the App. By downloading, installing, accessing, browsing or using the App, you accept and agree to these Terms which bind you legally. The Terms are entered into for the benefit of EIN and its affiliated companies (each an “Epson Company” and collectively the “Epson Companies") who may each enforce the same against you. If you do not agree to these Terms you are not permitted to use the App and you must immediately cease downloading, installing and/or using the App.

1.2 	The content provided in the App is intended for general informational purposes only. If you are a customer of EIN and/or an Epson Company, you may be subject to other agreements with them. These Terms apply to use of the App only and do not vary or alter any other contract or agreement which you may have entered into with the Epson Companies.

1.3 	If you experience any technical issues with the App, or you would like to contact us regarding these Terms, you may contact us by sending an email to ____________.

1.4 	In order to use the App, you must have a compatible device which meets the following minimum specifications: for Android, _______________. Any compatible device to which you download the App will be known as a "Device" for the purposes of these Terms. You confirm that you either own the applicable Device or if not owned by you, you have obtained permission to install and use the App on such Device. You accept responsibility for any use of the App on or in relation to such Device, whether or not such Device is owned by you or such use was made by you.

1.5 	In order to access the App, you must have an account with a valid username and password to be created by you.

2.	ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

2.1 	These Terms apply to the App, including any updates or supplements thereto. EIN may change or revise these Terms from time to time in its sole discretion, with or without notice to you. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions. Your access and use will be subject to the most current version of the Terms. Your use of the App after such revised Terms are made available will signify your acceptance of such revised Terms and your agreement to be bound by them.

2.2 	From time to time, updates to the App may be made available through the Play Store. Depending on the update, and whether you utilized the App Store or Play Store to download and access the App, you may not be able to use the App until you have installed the latest version. We will not be liable for damage that you could have avoided by installing the latest version of the App or for damage that was caused by you failing to correctly install the App or have in place the minimum system requirements.

2.3 	You confirm that you are of legal age in your country to form a binding contract and hereby agree to be bound by these Terms. If you are an employee or other representative of a business or other entity and you are using the App in your representative capacity, then you hereby represent that you are authorised to use the App as a representative of the entity and agree to these Terms on behalf such entity.

3.	PRIVACY

	Your submission of information, including personal information, through or in connection with the App (if any) is governed by the terms of our privacy policy as updated from time to time, available at https://www.epson.co.id/personaldatapolicy ("Privacy Policy") and you are deemed to have accepted the same in using the App.

4.	THIRD PARTY CONTENT

	The App may contain links to independent third-party websites or other applications ("Third-Party Sites"). Third Party Sites are not under our control, and you agree that we are not responsible for and do not endorse or monitor their content or privacy policies (if any). We expressly disclaim any liability for loss or damage sustained by you as a result of the accessing and use of Third-Party Sites and you hereby agree that you shall not hold us liable in whatever manner for such loss or damage.

5.	LICENSE

	Subject to these Terms, the Privacy Policy and Play Store Rules, we grant to you a non-exclusive, non-transferable, non-sublicensable, personal, limited, revocable license to use the App on the Devices for the Purpose. Any other use of the App is strictly prohibited. We reserve all rights in and to the App. EIN reserves the right to revoke this license at any time, in its sole discretion.

6.	LICENSE RESTRICTIONS

6.1 	Except as expressly permitted under these Terms, and unless prohibited by applicable law, you agree:
(a) 	not to copy, reproduce, republish, reuse, upload, post, transmit or distribute any content presented in or provided by the App, including without limitation for public or commercial purposes, including any text, images, audio and video;
(b) 	not to rent, lease, sub-license, loan, distribute, time-share, or translate the App in any way;
(c) 	not to make or cause alterations to, or modifications of, the whole or any part of the App, or permit the App or any part of it to be combined with, or become incorporated in, any other programs save that you may engage such third-party authorised by EIN to carry out such alterations and/or modifications of the App to suit your business purposes;
(d) 	not to disassemble, decompile, reverse-engineer or create derivative works based on the whole or any part of the App;
(e) 	not to sell, resell, or exploit the App in whole or in part (including object and source code), in any form to any person without prior written consent from us;
(f) 	not to remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices from the App.

7.	ADDITIONAL RESTRICTIONS

7.1 	You agree:
(a) 	not to use the App in any unlawful manner, for any unlawful or criminal purpose, or in any manner inconsistent with these Terms, or act fraudulently or maliciously, for example, by hacking into or inserting malicious code, including viruses, or harmful data, into the App;
(b) 	not to use the App to record, post or transmit any information that is defamatory, threatening, abusive, offensive, obscene, indecent, discriminatory or is otherwise objectionable or infringes on third party rights;
(c) 	not to use the App in a way that could damage, disable, overburden, impair or compromise our systems or security or interfere with other users, or restrict or inhibit any other users from using the App (including by hacking or defacing the App); and
(d) 	not to collect or harvest any information or data from the App or our systems or attempt to decipher any transmissions to or from the servers running the App, including, without limitation, by using any robot, spider, site search/retrieval application or other manual or automatic device to retrieve, index, "scrape," "data mine" or in any way gather the App content or reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the App without our prior written consent.

8.	INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS

8.1  	You hereby expressly acknowledge that (i) all intellectual property rights in and to the App belong to the Epson Companies, (ii) the rights granted herein are licensed to you, and (iii) you have no rights in, or to, the App or its content other than the right to use the App in accordance with these Terms.

8.2 	In the event that you elect to share information with the Epson Companies through the App in whatever manner, you agree and acknowledge that (i) all information supplied by you is either original to you, or you have the right to share it with the Epson Companies, (ii) the Epson Companies may utilize the information you supply, in whole or in part, in any manner in connection with the App, (iii) any modifications or improvements made to the App or Epson’s products or services as a result of your feedback are owned and controlled solely by the Epson Companies and (iv) you have no right, title or interest in or to the App as a result of sharing your feedback.

8.3 	All trademarks, service marks, trade names and logos whatsoever are proprietary to the Epson Companies. Nothing contained in this App shall be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark displayed in this App without the written permission of EIN. Your use of the trademarks displayed in this App, or any other content in this App, except as provided herein, is strictly prohibited. You acknowledge that you have no right to have access to the App in source code form.

9.	DISCLAIMER

9.1 	The App is provided 'as is' and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, EIN and its' directors, officers, employees, agents, representatives, licensors, third party providers and affiliates, exclude all representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, satisfactory quality, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement. Any reliance on or use of the App shall be at your sole risk. The Epson Companies and the Play Store, shall not have any obligation to furnish any maintenance and/or support services with respect to the App. We expressly disclaim any liability for loss or damage sustained by you as a result of the accessing and use of the App and you expressly agree that you shall not hold us liable to the same.

9.2 	We make no representation or warranty as to the completeness and/or accuracy of the information or content provided in the App. Such information is also subject to change at any time without notice to you.

9.3 	We do not warrant that the functions contained in the App will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected or that the App is free of viruses or other harmful components. We do not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the result of the use of the App. You agree to conduct your own due diligence to assess the accuracy, reliability and quality of all content provided by the App and hereby expressly agree not to hold us liable for any loss and/or damage resulting from the same.

9.4 	You assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair and/or correction in respect of your Device, whether or not the same is the result of your use of this App.

10.	LIMITED WARRANTY

10.1 	The App shall be validly licensed, of satisfactory quality, fit for Purpose and shall comply in all material respects with the description made available to you prior to downloading or installing it.

11.	AVAILABILITY

11.1 	We reserve the right, temporarily or permanently, in whole or in part, to modify, suspend or discontinue the App without notice for any reason without liability to you, except where prohibited by applicable law.

11.2 	In addition, you acknowledge that the App is provided over the internet and/or mobile networks and therefore the quality and availability of the App may be affected by factors outside of our reasonable control. Accordingly, we do not accept any responsibility for any connectivity issues that you may experience when using the App. In addition, you acknowledge and agree that you are responsible for obtaining and maintaining all telecommunications, broadband and/or computer hardware, equipment and services needed to access and use the App, and for paying any data charges that may be charged to you by your network provider in connection with your use of the App. You acknowledge and agree that you shall be responsible for paying any related fees that may be charged to you by your network and/or telecommunications provider.

12.	LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

12.1 	You agree that your use of the App and/or any Third-Party Sites shall be at your own risk. You further understand and agree that, to the fullest extent permitted under applicable law, EIN and/or the Epson Companies shall not be responsible and/or liable to you under these Terms, including without limitation to any loss, injury and/or damages (including but not limited to any special, indirect, consequential or punitive damages, lost profits, lost revenues or other incidental damages) arising out of the use, inability to use, or the result of use of the App.

13.	INDEMNIFICATION

13.1 	To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify us for any claims, actions, demands, losses, liabilities, damages, costs and expenses (including legal expenses and other costs, such as attorneys' fees) incurred by us that arise out of your use of the App. We reserve the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any claim brought by a third party in connection with your use of the App and you agree to render full assistance and cooperation in relation to any such claim.

14.	TERMINATION

14.1 	EIN and/or the Epson Companies may discontinue, suspend or modify the App at any time without notice and may block, terminate or suspend your access to the App at any time without notice for any reason in its sole discretion, even if access continues to be allowed to others. Upon termination, you must cease use of the App and remove it from all applicable Device(s).

15.	EVENTS OUTSIDE OUR CONTROL

15.1 	We will not be liable or responsible for any failure to perform, or delay in performance of, any of our obligations under these Terms that is caused by any act or event beyond our reasonable control, including any failure of public or private telecommunications networks.

16.	RELATIONSHIP WITH THE PLAY STORE

16.1 	With respect to downloading the App, you agree to comply with the Play Store Rules. You acknowledge that the availability of the App may be dependent on the Play Store from which you receive the App. You acknowledge these Terms are between you and EIN and not with the Play Store. The Play Store shall not be responsible for the App, the content thereof, maintenance, support services, and warranty therefor, and addressing any claims relating thereto (e.g., product liability, legal compliance, or intellectual property infringement).

17.	LAW AND JURISDICTION

17.1 	These Terms shall be subject to, governed by, and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Indonesia. Any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach, termination or invalidity thereof shall be settled by arbitration in accordance with the UNCITRAL Arbitration Rules as at present in force. The number of arbitrators shall be one (1), and such arbitrator shall be appointed by EIN. The place and seat of arbitration shall be Jakarta, Indonesia. The decision of the arbitrator shall be final and binding on the Parties. The language used in the arbitration proceedings shall be English.

18.	GENERAL

18.1 	We may transfer our rights and/or obligations and/or delegate our duties under this Agreement to any Epson Company. You shall not assign, transfer, or otherwise dispose of your rights and obligations under these Terms.

18.2 	The rights and remedies provided by these Terms are cumulative and the use of any one right or remedy by us shall not preclude or waive our right to use any or all other remedies. Such rights and remedies are given in addition to any other rights that we may have by laws, rules, regulations, judicial orders, ordinances or otherwise.

18.3 	If any provision(s) of these Terms is found to be illegal, void or unenforceable under any law that is applicable hereto or if any court of competent jurisdiction in a final decision so determines, these Terms shall continue in force save that such provision(s) shall be deemed to be excised here from with effect from the date of the decision by such court of competent jurisdiction.

18.4 	These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us and supersedes all previous verbal or written proposals and agreements relating to the subject matter hereof.

18.5 	Save for any Epson Company, a person or entity who is not a party to this Agreement shall not have any right under this Agreement to enforce any term of this Agreement, regardless of whether such person or entity has been identified by name, as a member of a class or as answering a particular description. For the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this clause shall affect the rights of any permitted assignee or transferee of these Terms.

18.6 	We are an independent contractor and no agency, partnership, joint venture or employment relationship is created as a result of these Terms. Neither of us has any authority of any kind to bind the other in any respect.
</string>
</resources>
